A Guide to the Richmond Urban Institute Archives 1979-1986
Virginia Commonwealth University, James Branch Cabell Library
- Series VIII Other Organizations 1979-1988
  - Impact 1985, n.d. (Box-folder 29:2)
  - Leadership Metro Richmond 1984 (Box-folder 29:3)
  - Metropolitan Foundation n.d. (Box-folder 29:4)
  - Miscellaneous organizations 1981-1988 (Box-folder 29:5)
  - Miscellaneous organizations 1985 (Box-folder 29:6)
  - Miscellaneous organizations 1985-1986 (Box-folder 29:7)
  - Miscellaneous organizations 1985-1988 (Box-folder 30:1)
  - Moral RE-Armament Conference n.d. (Box-folder 30:2)
  - Neighborhoods, USA 1984-1988, n.d. (Box-folder 30:3)
  - Organization Development Consultants n.d. (Box-folder 30:4)
  - Parent-Child Task Force, Virginia Department of Health 1984-1986 (Box-folder 30:5)
  - Park School 1984-1985 (Box-folder 30:6)
  - Peter-Paul Development Center n.d. (Box-folder 30:7)
  - Pretend, Inc. 1986 (Box-folder 30:8)
  - Richmond Chamber of Commerce n.d. (Box-folder 30:9)
  - Richmond City Council 1979 (Box-folder 30:10)
  - Richmond First Club 1984-1986 (Box-folder 30:11)
  - Richmond Food Stamp Committee and Anti-Hunger Coalition n.d. (Box-folder 30:12)
  - Richmond Metropolitan Habitat for Humanity n.d. (Box-folder 30:13)
  - Richmond Peace Exchange 1984, n.d. (Box-folder 30:14)
  - Richmond Public Schools 1984 (Box-folder 30:15)
  - Richmond Renaissance 1981-1982 (Box-folder 30:16)
  - Richmond Urban Forum 1981-1982, 1984 (Box-folder 30:17)
  - Richmond Urban League n.d. (Box-folder 30:18)
  - Virginia Association of Fund-Raising Executives 1985 (Box-folder 30:19)
  - Virginia Council of Churches (Box-folder 30:20)
  - Virginia General Assembly 1984-1985 (Box-folder 30:21)
  - Virginia Society of Association Executives 1985 (Box-folder 31:1)
  - Virginia Supplemental Retirement System 1985 (Box-folder 31:2)
  - United Way 1984-1985, n.d. (Box-folder 31:3)
  - Youth Employment Advisory Committee 1984, 1986 (Box-folder 31:4)
- Series IX Reference 1977--1984
  - Census Material 1980 (Box-folder 31:5)
  - Conference Centers 1981, n.d. (Box-folder 31:6)
  - Foundation Grans 1977-1980, n.d. (Box-folder 31:7)
  - Kindred Organizations n.d. (Box-folder 31:8)
  - Linkages 1979-1983, n.d. (Box-folder 31:9)
  - Roslyn Retreat Center 1979-1984, n.d. (Box-folder 31:10)
- Series X Scrapbooks and Albums
  - Account Book, School of Social Work 1983 (Box 1)
  - U.S. Department of Housing and Urban Development Certificate (Box 1)
  - Institute of Research and Planning Office 1970-1980s (Box 1)
  - Photoablum 1980s (Box 2)
  - WWBT 12 inch video tape (Box 3)
  - Video-Julie Seward (Box 3)